Your Bitcoin is sitting idle.
What if it could generate yield every single week?
Introducing sBTC Options Vault —
the first covered call options platform
built on Bitcoin, powered by Stacks.
Here's how it works.
An option is a contract between two parties.
The buyer pays a small premium —
say 0.05 sBTC —
for the right to profit if Bitcoin's price
rises above a set strike price before expiry.
The risk? Only the premium you paid.
The reward? Potentially massive upside.
Getting started is simple.
Connect your Leather or Xverse wallet,
and you'll instantly see the vault dashboard —
total value locked,
current share price, and the active epoch.
Everything updates in real-time
from on-chain data.
Head to the Market page
to browse available options.
Each listing shows the strike price,
premium cost, and collateral backing.
Found one you like?
Click "Buy Option,"
confirm the transaction in your wallet,
and your premium flows directly
into the vault through
the Stacks blockchain.
Your position is now live —
fully on-chain, fully transparent.
Once you've bought an option,
track it in real-time.
The system pulls live Bitcoin prices
from the on-chain oracle
and calculates your profit
and loss instantly.
Green means you're "In the Money" —
Bitcoin is above your strike
and you're in profit.
Orange means "Out of the Money" —
but remember, your maximum loss
is always capped at the premium you paid.
Here's where it gets exciting.
When Bitcoin settles above your strike price,
you're in the money.
The payout formula is simple:
collateral times the price difference,
divided by the settlement price.
In this example — with a strike of $90,000
and settlement at $100,000 —
your 0.05 sBTC premium
turns into 0.50 sBTC.
That's a 900% return on your investment.
And if Bitcoin stays below the strike?
Your option simply expires.
You lose only the premium —
0.05 sBTC. That's it.
Unlike leveraged trading
where you can get liquidated,
with options your downside
is always defined and limited.
You know your maximum risk
before you even enter the trade.
Ready to profit?
Claim your payout with one click
and it flows straight to your wallet.
sBTC Options Vault —
structured yield on Bitcoin,
fully on-chain, fully transparent.
Start trading now.